[{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664120221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":10061,"timeElapsed":46107},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664129629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":9407,"timeElapsed":55515},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664133077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3447,"timeElapsed":58963},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664139357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":6279,"timeElapsed":65243},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664142213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2855,"timeElapsed":68099},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664146805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4591,"timeElapsed":72691},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664149525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2719,"timeElapsed":75411},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664155733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6207,"timeElapsed":81619},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664160021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4287,"timeElapsed":85907},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664173965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":12863,"timeElapsed":99851},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664178237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4271,"timeElapsed":104123},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664181133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2895,"timeElapsed":107019},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664183189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2055,"timeElapsed":109075},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664186805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3615,"timeElapsed":112691},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664190165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3359,"timeElapsed":116051},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664192765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2599,"timeElapsed":118651},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664195645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2879,"timeElapsed":121531},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664197965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2320,"timeElapsed":123851},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664208293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":9095,"timeElapsed":134179},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664210357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2063,"timeElapsed":136243},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664213685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3327,"timeElapsed":139571},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664215901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2216,"timeElapsed":141787},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664220357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4455,"timeElapsed":146243},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664223013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2655,"timeElapsed":148899},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664225949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2935,"timeElapsed":151835},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664231285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":5335,"timeElapsed":157171},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664232901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1615,"timeElapsed":158787},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664241325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7256,"timeElapsed":167211},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664244077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2751,"timeElapsed":169963},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664247557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3479,"timeElapsed":173443},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664248709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1152,"timeElapsed":174595},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664253869,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5159,"timeElapsed":179755},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664256325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2456,"timeElapsed":182211},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664258821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2495,"timeElapsed":184707},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664262213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3392,"timeElapsed":188099},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664264621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2407,"timeElapsed":190507},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664275613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9640,"timeElapsed":201499},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664278429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2815,"timeElapsed":204315},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664280885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2456,"timeElapsed":206771},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664282685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1799,"timeElapsed":208571},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664285797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3111,"timeElapsed":211683},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664288789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2992,"timeElapsed":214675},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664291365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2575,"timeElapsed":217251},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664293502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2136,"timeElapsed":219388},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664294829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1326,"timeElapsed":220715},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664306205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":9159,"timeElapsed":232091},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664309149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2943,"timeElapsed":235035},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664311485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2335,"timeElapsed":237371},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664313253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1767,"timeElapsed":239139},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664317757,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4503,"timeElapsed":243643},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664320005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2247,"timeElapsed":245891},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664323141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":3136,"timeElapsed":249027},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664326446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3304,"timeElapsed":252332},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664328326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1879,"timeElapsed":254212},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664338093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":7775,"timeElapsed":263979},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664339725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1632,"timeElapsed":265611},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664342989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3263,"timeElapsed":268875},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":271067},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664353261,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8080,"timeElapsed":279147},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664356645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3383,"timeElapsed":282531},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664359621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2975,"timeElapsed":285507},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664362965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3343,"timeElapsed":288851},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664365541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2575,"timeElapsed":291427},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664367661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2119,"timeElapsed":293547},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664372837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3919,"timeElapsed":298723},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664375853,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3015,"timeElapsed":301739},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664381949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6095,"timeElapsed":307835},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664384269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2319,"timeElapsed":310155},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664386589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2320,"timeElapsed":312475},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664390309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3719,"timeElapsed":316195},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664392197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1888,"timeElapsed":318083},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664394029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1831,"timeElapsed":319915},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664397269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3239,"timeElapsed":323155},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664399909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2640,"timeElapsed":325795},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664423021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":21919,"timeElapsed":348907},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664424653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1631,"timeElapsed":350539},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664429437,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4783,"timeElapsed":355323},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664431197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":1760,"timeElapsed":357083},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664434301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3103,"timeElapsed":360187},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664437517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3215,"timeElapsed":363403},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664439373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":1855,"timeElapsed":365259},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664441597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2223,"timeElapsed":367483},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664459341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":17743,"timeElapsed":385227},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664467965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":7271,"timeElapsed":393851},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664469637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1671,"timeElapsed":395523},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664472581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2943,"timeElapsed":398467},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664473877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1295,"timeElapsed":399763},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664476117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2239,"timeElapsed":402003},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664478405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":2288,"timeElapsed":404291},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664480797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":406683},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664482669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1871,"timeElapsed":408555},{"subjectID":"yef8d2mxov","prolificID":"60cf0d251a90eb823bc9b740","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214fb28366d7f2cee5d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664484253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1584,"timeElapsed":410139}]